Chengcheng became a doctor.
Will she be exposed?
It's a private clinic.
I've told them in advance.
Don't worry.
I'm cured.
Sorry.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
See you never.
SPECIALTY RECOMMENDATION
BRAISED BEEF TENDON WITH SECRET SAUCE
NO PARKING, ILLEGAL PARKING MONITORED
THE BOND BAR
MI YOGA, INSHAN GYM
What's wrong with you?
You only got dumped.
Do you have to die for this?
Ask anyone on the street.
Who hasn't been dumped before?
You usually look decent,
but you're so immature and irrational.
It's okay. You can cry.
It's okay to cry for getting dumped,
but you shouldn't die for this, okay?
Tang Qi?
I didn't want to die.
I just didn't notice
the traffic light turned red.
Thank you.
I'm fine now.
You can leave.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected for the moment.
Please try again later.
Why are you back again?
It started to rain.
You don't have an umbrella.
I'll walk with you.
No need.
Green light.
I just remembered I had something to do.
Same direction.
Well, thank you.
It's okay. Let's go.
You…
Why don't you watch the road?
The manhole isn't properly covered.
It's dangerous.
The umbrella is orange.
Okay.
Hello.
At the intersection of Heping Road
and Chunguang Road,
the manhole isn't covered.
People might get hurt.
Please send someone to fix it.
Yes, people might get hurt.
Tang Qi is so kind.
Okay, thanks.
- Let's go.
- Wait a minute.
Okay, thanks.
That's Tang Qi.
I said I didn't want to die.
You don't pause in the middle.
Once you get home, I'll leave.
It seems we scared her.
XINYUAN GROCERY STORE
Did you see a girl in red pass by?
She went that way.
Thanks.
Didn't you say her?
The girl who got scared
was in red.
I was absent-minded
and didn't notice her clothes.
Now that you're safe at home, I'll leave.
Su Chengcheng.
What's wrong?
Do you want to come in?
Are you really not going to invite me in?
No.
I'm already here.
Aren't you bored alone?
I can chat with you.
I have a dryer and a hairdryer.
You can dry your hair and clothes.
No need. I'll just head home.
It's in another direction.
Your body is weak,
so you might catch a cold.
If you get caught in the rain,
you'll take a day off on Monday.
You knew I was lying.
Thank you for taking me home.
Then I won't be polite.
Actually, I'm quite healthy.
I took days off because of emergencies.
I promise I won't do it again.
Go to the bathroom
to change the wet clothes.
- Okay.
- The bathroom is…
over there.
The layouts of redecorated old houses
are pretty much the same.
I went to my friend's house before.
I know where the bathroom is.
Oh.
The laundry room is next door.
- And the dryer is inside.
- Okay.
Here's the hairdryer.
The towel is clean.
- I didn't use it.
- Thanks.
I didn't want to die.
I just didn't notice
the traffic light turned red.
He really didn't notice that?
I was overthinking it.
He didn't want to die.
I'm a tetrachromat.
We can see a hundred times more colors
than common people do.
Did you see a girl in red pass by?
Oh no. Something's wrong with his eyes.
I'm sure you didn't have dinner.
It takes time to dry the clothes.
We can eat something.
Thanks.
It's just simple food,
but at least he can cook,
so his eyesight is fine.
Can't he see colors clearly?
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice it.
It got stained when I was drawing.
I washed the clothes,
but I couldn't clean the color.
I'll get another one.
No need.
Just a little paint.
I need to change back
into my clothes later anyway.
Let's eat.
Then I'll eat.
He can see the color.
Was I overthinking it again?
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
Oh no. I have a really good appetite.
I like everything.
Why is he imitating the way I eat?
Do his eyes also have decision fatigue?
It's so nice to eat hot wontons
on a rainy day.
What's wrong?
The editors arranged a dinner for artists.
There's a rival
who'd play nasty tricks
every time we meet.
I heard she got engaged.
She'll definitely try every means
to insult me.
You don't want to go?
Why should I give up this opportunity
just because of her?
Not only will I go,
but I will dress up for it
and piss her off.
Come here.
This is called parrotfish.
Parrotfish?
Because they're
as colorful as a parrot's feathers.
Its formal name is blackspot razorfish.
That fish is so pretty.
It's called angelfish
because it swims smoothly,
like an angel.
It's from the family Cichlidae.
There are Bluespotted Angelfish,
Freshwater Angelfish,
and Albino Red Eye Angelfish.
What is this one?
It's kissing fish or kissing gouramis,
because they like to kiss each other.
So romantic.
The two fish that were kissing
are both male.
The kissing behavior
is also between same-sex fish.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
I mean, they don't kiss each other
out of friendship or love,
but…
for fighting.
Do you mean they were fighting?
We naturally consider
kissing fish as a symbol of love,
but when
two kissing fish meet,
they will instinctively extend
their serrated lips
to collide forcefully with each other
to protect their territory
until one of them retreats.
Pride and prejudice are everywhere.
Humans are so arrogant.
Not only we, but also fish have
to bear others' misunderstanding
and prejudice.
No matter how humans
interpret their meaning,
they're always being themselves.
You're right.
We only need to try to be ourselves.
Other people's interpretation
doesn't matter.
Do you know something?
Do you know my rival?
I swear I don't know anything or anyone.
However, disputes between humans
are pretty much the same.
For fame and interest,
out of pride and prejudice.
Didn't you say it yourself?
Well said. You can write a book.
You're the real expert here.
I'm so flattered.
Hello, Lin Yuan.
I suddenly got my period
and I got caught in the rain.
My stomach hurts, and I want to go home.
Can you pick me up?
Where are you? I'm coming.
Tang Qi's place.
You're…
Humans are worse than fish.
What?
I mean, humans' pride and prejudice
are despicable.
It's an emergency. Hurry up.
I'm coming.
My friend is in trouble.
I need to save her.
- See you next time.
- I--
She clearly doesn't like you.
Gu Yu, I never expected
this would happen to you.
You're not fish,
so how do you know if they are happy?
Hello.
My phone was on silent mode,
so I didn't hear it.
Okay, I'm coming.
Are you going home?
Tang Qi needs me. I'm going to his house.
I'm also going there. Same direction.
Why don't we…?
Be careful.
We can't be in the same car.
What's wrong?
My car ran out of fuel.
Can you give me a ride?
Yes.
Su Chengcheng.
Are you not feeling well?
My… My stomach hurts.
You should rest. Give it to me.
- No need!
- Come on.
It's okay.
Did he see it or not?
You're weak and easy to get sick,
so you need to be more careful.
Don't get caught in the rain.
I'm pretty healthy.
This is an accident.
I promise
I won't take a day off on Monday.
You can rest if you need to.
Don't push yourself.
Quan Shengtang, the person
who crashed you in tennis,
was me.
If you don't feel well, go home early.
I called a premier car on DiDi.
It's more comfortable.
It's about to arrive.
When did you call it?
When you were drying your hair.
You're always so thoughtful.
But I already asked
Lin Yuan to pick me up.
Gu Yu said her car ran out of fuel.
How did he know that?
They're here. You can ask her.
When did you two become so close?
Long story.
Gu Yu is warm-hearted
and always free on weekends,
so he often helps me collect materials.
Gu Yu is warm-hearted
and free on weekends?
Are we talking about the same person?
It doesn't matter.
What happened to you?
You tried so hard
to make Fang Jin disappear.
However, you didn't draw lines with him
but went to his house.
I was afraid that he wanted to die,
so I took him home.
Tang Qi wanted to die?
Are we talking about the same person?
Maybe I overthought it.
But he's been weird.
Something must be wrong.
Stop staring at me.
You're making me nervous.
Who got in the car first?
Su Chengcheng.
Good guess.
I didn't guess it.
I saw it.
My eyes
can only see the color
of Su Chengcheng now.
Your eyes can only see
the color of Su Chengcheng?
What does it mean?
OPHTHALMOLOGY EXAM REPORT
The fundus
is fine.
And the cornea
has no problem.
You're healthy.
Tang,
have you faced stressful situations
in your work and life recently?
What do you mean?
Here's the thing.
A patient once
suddenly became blind.
However, according to the exam results,
it was because
the graduate entrance examination
was too stressful.
Your eyes haven't shown
any organic lesions.
Given this situation,
I think it was caused
by your mental health.
I suggest you find a psychiatrist
to get mental treatment.
But it's not that I can't see any colors.
I can see the color of a colleague.
No matter what object she touches,
I can see the color of that thing.
I'm not a psychiatrist,
so I can't explain this.
But I think this is related
to your subconscious mind.
Maybe it wants to tell you something.
Maybe this person is the key
to curing your eyes.
If it's possible,
you can try to interact more
with this person
to see if it can get better.
Doctor Chen asked you
to interact more with Su Chengcheng,
so give it a try.
Su Chengcheng is not a monster.
You can make friends with her.
Don't be so reluctant.
I'm not reluctant.
I used to be biased against her,
but now she's completely changed.
She's different.
You were biased against her?
Why?
Tell me about your youth.
This is about my eyes.
Why are you always gossiping?
Doctor Chen said maybe Su Chengcheng
is the key to curing your eyes.
I just want
to find that lock for you.
Doctor Chen is an ophthalmologist,
not a psychiatrist.
Then tell me.
Why can you only see
the color of Su Chengcheng?
I don't know.
Didn't you say you were busy?
Why are you treating us to a meal?
I'm in trouble right now
and want you to help me
confirm the result.
What trouble?
Do you need our help?
- No need.
- He can handle it.
By the way,
didn't you say you want us
to help you confirm the result?
Have you got the result?
I've figured it out.
I met you,
Zhou Jinli,
and my parents.
My best friend,
my closest work partner,
and my family
are colorless in my eyes.
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
I'm not reluctant
to get along with Su Chengcheng.
I just don't understand.
Why is it Su Chengcheng?
Why is it only her?
Stop!
Stop the car!